[{"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.15", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2312", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3340", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Huawei Model": "P30 Lite"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.84", "Display Resolution": "2280x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "400", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Xiaomi Model": "6 pro", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "1080*2460", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UNIWA"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "3inch", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6739", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.528", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10600", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.7", "Display Resolution": "1334x750", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1715", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Apple Model": "Apple iPhone 6s", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "4K (2160p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MEIZU"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.55", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "144Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "80W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67", "Display Resolution": "2712x1220", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 13 Pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5180", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MEIZU"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224840MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "40W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 888", "Built in radiator": "no", "Meizu Model": "18spro"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "KXD"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52\"", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP,2MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500mah", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "FHD+ 1080x2400", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4380", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "fuffi"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52", "Display Resolution": "1480x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3250", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67 Inch", "Display Resolution": "2712*1220", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Xiaomi HyperCharge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "MIUI 14"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi K70E", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.35''", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"CPU": "Adreno 512", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "redmi note 7", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OnePlus"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.41", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Gray", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 240 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Oneplus Model": "7", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 855", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "3.2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "15080", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Blackview Model": "BV9300", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.8\"", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "": "295369929", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS,pse", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G80", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Amoi"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "1600*960", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5200", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "EIS stabilization,Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "POCO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.74", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Function 5": "Xiaomi phone", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "POCO Model": "POCO C65", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Amoi"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "5", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000mAh", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "6000-7499mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "fuffi"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.26''", "Display Resolution": "960x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Snapdragon 8 Gen 2"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.73", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen,Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224832MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0,Charge Turbo", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "MIUI 14"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "EIS stabilization,Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Xiaomi Model": "Xiaomi 13 Ultra", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "POCO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.74", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Function 6": "Xiaomi phone", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "POCO Model": "POCO C65", "MTK Model": "Helio G85", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67&quot;", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Flexible Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "FlashCharge", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Note 12 Pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "2532x1170", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2775", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "Used", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Apple Model": "iPhone 12 Pro", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "TECNO"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6\u2018\u2019", "Display Resolution": "1560x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400*1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Bluetooth": "Bluetooth 5.0", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 12", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.71\u201d", "Display Resolution": "1650 x 720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Charging": "10W in-box charger", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi 12C", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Screen Material": "Corning Gorilla Glass 3", "Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "itel"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "720x1600", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.56", "Display Resolution": "1612x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Bluetooth": "Bluetooth 5.0", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Note 12", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Hotwav"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6\u2018\u2019", "Display Resolution": "1612x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5160", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.56", "Display Resolution": "1612x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5200", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"ROM": "256GB,support TF card up to 1TB extended", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2460x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "100MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "Watch", "OUKITEL Model": "WP30 PRO", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Video recording resolution": "2K (1440p) 120 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Dimensity 1000+", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.5inches", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u22641MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no"}, "Other": {"Official Standard": "Yes", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6580", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.73", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4880", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "xiaomi 14 Pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.35''", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"CPU": "Adreno 512", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "note 7 pro", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2400", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "66W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "HarmonyOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Huawei Model": "Nova 11 SE"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "2532*1170", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2815", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "Used", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Apple Model": "iphone 12", "Language": "English,Russian", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.97", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224848MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "9se", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic,1"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7''", "Display Resolution": "1650x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Network": "2G,3G,4G", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "295369929", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.8", "Display Resolution": "1560x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card,1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Samsung Model": "A20E", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "KR(Origin)", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.8\"", "Display Resolution": "2460x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "Other", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "66W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"C2K": "BC0/BC1", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2600mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Official Standard": "Yes (Charger Not Included)", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "HD (720p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6739", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "2532 x 1170", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "Other", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card+1 eSIM"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "Used", "Apple Model": "iphone", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "itel"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "720x1600", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {}]